Can you hear me?
Hello?
Was able to solve it now. Sorry, I'm what's coming. How are you?
All good, and you?
I'm good as well, thank you. Happy Wednesday.
Great. Yeah, I mean middle of the week.
Yeah, like we're closer to weekend but not that, not that close yet.
100%. Yeah.
Cool.
Tell me how can I help you?
Yeah, thank you for, for joining the call.
I know that we are super all super busy but what I as the title of the call says, I'm
working on preparing a summit rapid.
Paul and I think a couple of like one or two weeks ago about working on locking next summit date
so that we can start planning, doing research, budgeting and processing visas if needed. So we are penciling two summits.
One that would be like a regional summit or like bot summit kind of thing.
So that's why you know like couple of weeks ago, well we brought the subject of potentially working on an
engineering summit in Europe. So that's like on top of mind but open to hear other ideas as well.
And yeah, so we are working like we are thinking on having potentially that bot Summit on late Q2 after
wrapping up fundraising.
That's the expectation we have regarding series B and doing and planning global summit for Q4 as we did last
year, something around October of November.
So basically what I'm doing, it's not only gathering some thoughts that you can have but also working on defining
your availability.
If you happen to have already plans or whatever, you know, personal stuff planned for around May and June or
October, November would be great to know.
I have a spreadsheet, same as I did last time where basically everyone flag if they are free or not
ideal or whatever you can open in there and if you already have plans, please. Market.
So that way I know which dates are not ideal for you or not available.
Okay. Yeah, I can, I can both days. Honestly, that's for. For me, like, for example, it's fine.
So we are thinking between October, November or May. And this one is May. June is specially for engineering, right?
Yeah, we're thinking engineering.
I was, I just talked with Evgeny about potentially having those like product design team or you know, if we,
if we wanted to bring someone from support. He was like, I mean if it's only.
He was like, if it's only engineering, it's.
It's kind of better because they can focus all the week on engineering work, but he can adapt if we
want to include any other team to work with them as well.
Yeah, so yeah, I think like it would make much sense to have engineering and product design.
Yeah, that's of course they can collaborate together and they can work together on the different stuff.
So this, this way, like, especially because most of the engineers work with the product designers directly.
I think having this in person week where they are actually working, they can define the things and everything, I
think it makes more sense.
We can also dedicate this week on roadmap planning, that kind of stuff, you know. For example.
For example, is Paul planning to attend the engineering summit or. No?
I think he's planning to attend.
I think that he wants to lock the day so he can plan his schedule.
So I assume he's planning to join and given I'm talking with exec team, I assume that we are going
to try to have all the exact team as well together, such in personal work.
Yeah, that's what I asked already to Dennis if he was.
He think it makes sense to have the same team as well for like working in person because he also
can use that week to collaborate with them closely.
Evgeny said that he can adapt the week to do like a collaboration between engineering and design.
And I asked him already about potentially bringing support. He says that maybe it makes sense to bring Anne.
As you know, she seems she's working closely to engineering.
He says like, maybe it's gonna be more productive to her.
Like, I mean, Evgeny's thought right now is like, maybe Ann will be having like active collaboration only one or
two days of the whole week. But I was like, okay.
I mean, I, I think that if we can bring her, it makes sense because it can also promote having
this in person collaboration as well with guinea, since they work closely.
So yeah, I mean he said that it makes sense and he's fine with.
That if we can include there as well.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, might. Might make sense. We just need to define what that summit is for. Right.
If it's for this, like, it would make total sense if we want to discuss the road map and work
on the next cycle and everything.
So it would be like by the end of the cycle, we could do the retro and also plan the
next cycle. At least from the.
Check if it overlap. Because I already planned all the. All this year planning weeks.
Let me see if it overlaps. It. It might overlap because this May. Yeah. No, it won't. Over.
Well, we could try to push it because the last planning for Q2 would be between April 20th planning week
and retro the week of April 13th.
And if G cannot travel in April, he said that after April he can travel. So.
Okay, what? We don't. Why don't we do it by end of June then?
Yeah. Wait. Should be very February 1st.
March, April 2nd. Yeah. May, June. We can do it in the end of June.
Yeah. Because we have planning week. Yeah. We have retro week on June, Monday, 8th, and planning week on 15.
So we could do it during retro or planning. Like, we can play around with that. Okay, Planning week twice.
I have a. I have an issue here with my. Okay. But yeah, it's in June.
I'm gonna fix the scale because I have an issue.
No worries. Because like, this way, if.
If we want to bring the exec team, the exec team can focus on the roadmap and everything, while the
engineering team can have their own goals on what needs to be done. Right.
The main thing here is to guarantee that the engineers can actually focus on their work and there is a
clear goal that needs to be achieved during that week.
So I remember Evgeny mentioned that, like, hey, we can do a one week summit wherever with all the engineers,
and we define the goals, and during that week, we only work on those specific goals, like in person. Right.
Because when the summit is smaller, the best outcome would be if some good amount of work is done. Right.
Because we won't have that. Like, we won't have activities. There is no, like too much outside dinners or whatever.
The focus is like that together
go to the nurse or something like that. Yeah, exactly.
Because like the main focus of it, it's get together and work on something specific, given we are spending a
lot of money to bring everybody together.
So I would speak with Evgeny and have you guinea define what would be the outcome of this summit.
Yeah, yeah. We haven't defined it yet. Like Paul told me, like, generally like.
Evaluate which teams and which, you know, like kind of bots are going to be like joining potentially.
We talk about engineering and I think that my, my first thought is engineering because for example, by September last
year we did with customer success in Bogota.
So I think that it makes more sense to do it with engineering.
Yeah.
And this is also the biggest team that we have at Arxiv and they are the ones that have more
things tied to them. Plus even we are recruiting new people.
So the team like we recruited already, Eugene and I expect we will hire another person by the end of
this month, etc. So it will be definitely make sense for them to get in person.
I, I just think, Emily, from your side, just guarantee that the outcome is clearly defined so we can also
justify the return on investment.
Yes, that's what I'm, that's what I'm working the rapid because you know, I'm gonna propose three or two potential
options based on that. So I'm gonna include this feedback as well.
Like hey, doing it either like doing it inside, doing cycle planning to, so we can work on roadmap, whatever.
And we can also like have decide whether all the exact same.
So I'm gonna evaluate like different a scenarios based on this and add it on the rapid dog that I
plan to share by end of week.
So, so that way I gather like a specific feedback from everyone and Paul has everyone's perspective.
Okay, cool, sounds good. And for the general summit. Yeah, October, November sounds like a good option.
We just research the countries especially now given you have like a better understanding of the budget that we spend
in Turkey, we can factor it in to see if there are cheaper countries, for example, that, that we could
use.
Yes, I'm gonna, I, I've been pushing this a little bit, but I'm gonna work as well on doing like
a forecast with the budget we spend.
So we can like what I'm thinking to do is calculate cost per person approximately and then we can properly
forecast with the, you know, future hires as well.
Okay.
Because you're gonna have a budget bump given. Yeah, we're gonna be like bigger.
I think we, you won't be able to have a clear understanding till at least middle or end of fundraise
because it will depend a lot on of the fundraise. How much, how many people are we going to be.
Yeah.
But since we have forecast, I can also plan to have two budgets.
I can have like, like meet a scenario with not that amount of team members joining and an scenario after
fundraise with a lot of people joining the team.
Yeah, it could make sense. Like, if you have time to work on it, definitely. It could be an option.
Yeah, I think it's valuable to spend some time working on it.
Because that way we have a better understanding on what we need, what budget we need. So, yeah. Okay.
This is super helpful, Andre. Thank you so much for giving and sharing your insights. I'm gonna try.
I mean, I'm gonna also talk to Paul to see if we can also, like, collaborate more on planning summits,
like, in terms of HR as well, to get you more involved. So, yeah, I'm gonna.
I'm gonna continue working and chatting with the team and let you know.
Okay, cool. Sounds good. Thank you, Emily. Bye.
Bye. Have a good one.
Bye for now.